Hello, welcome to my channel Hrithik Technical
Support, in this video we will tell you
how to take health insurance in Policy Bazaar, okay so first of all
you guys open policybazar.com,
okay then as you open it you have to
click on view all products,
after clicking here you will
get the option of health in health insurance, one CR health
cover means 1 crore health health cover, you will
see insurance, Arogya Sanjeev,
you will get a scheme, then family health
insurance, cancer insurance, now it depends on
which insurance you want to take,
now as our topic was that
we want to take health insurance, so we
will click on health insurance,
okay then first you will find top plans for
you with up to 25% discount, whether you are male
or female, currently we are male here, okay
after clicking on mail, the
members you want to insure, so currently we
want to take ourselves, we will click on self, then
click on continue,
please select at least one member, self done,
brother, click on continue, then
you will get your  You have to select your age. OK,
after selecting your age, you have to click
on select your city, then you have to enter your city, then
you have to enter your name, you have to enter your number, then
you have to click on continue,
okay, so 100% almost our
medical history is complete, you have to
enter if you do not have
diabetes, blood pressure,
any surgery or thyroid, asthma, other
disease, nothing at the moment,
we will click on none of this, then does your office
provide health insurance for you,
currently none of our offices provide us, then
we will click on view no,
click on view plan,
now the next interface will be,
you will see this type of plan in which
we can see almost 78 plans of all the companies at present,
OK and first comes the plan of Care Health
Insurance, in which we are told
that you will have to pay 874 for the month
and this amount will cover your ₹ lakh,
okay, no room rent limit of 10 lakh  5000
Enable Bonus Unlimited Restoration of Cover
Second comes the insurance of 5 lakhs Now
look at this Superstar insurance,
we will click on View Wall Features and
see its complete policy
that claim paid within three months room
rent limit any category then Renal Bonus and
Pre Hospitalization Coverage then Post
Hospital Coverage 180 days Okay now look at the
insurance company that provides you here, first of all
you should
see their details so that you do
not face any problem later, you should see their policy,
for example, I am thinking
here that I want to take
Active One Economy
health insurance from Aditya Birla Capital,
so I will click on this, you can see the amount
of cover per month, you can also see the
amount of cover, you can also increase it, the maximum
here is also seen to be 2 crores
and here you
can see the period of C that it will be for one year,
your
8497 in two years
34200 in the third year, 0000 okay, so in the three-year plan
you will save up to 00,
in the two-year plan
you will save around 5000, okay, now here
you will have to turn on something, you have to turn on claim protect,
you have to turn on super credit,
then click on view more riders, then
you have to do some more add-ons
like second medical opinion, if you want to add on, then
you can advance this add-on condition here,
now here you
can see the base premium of one year is
8497,
you can see the room rent type and you can see the preferred
provider network,
and if you want to advance then you can
see it, now for now we will have to pay the total premium of
15390, so
we will click on proceed to ok, if you want to do OPD cover then you
can do that, for now we will
click on no I don't want OPD coverage, then
we will click on proceed to personal,
ok now  After coming here, you will have to
enter the details like first you have to
enter your name which will be in your PAN card,
marital status will be in Aadhar card,
we are single, for now we will enter the email here,
you have to enter your PAN card number,
okay then you will have to enter your GST number,
so you can also enter the GST number,
and second you will have to enter your date of
birth, in occupation you will have to enter
what you do, then you have to
enter your height, how much is your height, then
enter your height in inches, then
you will enter your weight, how much is your weight, then
here you will have to enter your address, then the
sector of the colony, which
extra, then
you will enter the contact details, like email
address, mobile number, emergency mobile, PF,
PEP details, here
you have to click on proceed to medical question, and after this,
second you have to fill in your medical details, then
you have to enter your nominee, which is
very easy, then you proceed and make the
payment.  You can, okay, so in this way
you can get health insurance in the policy market,
so the topic is covered
in the next video, Jai Mata Di.